Techical Business Analyst ~ 3 months of experience

DUONG NGUYEN

1. 0946 292 494

duongnguyen.22@icloud.com <u>1</u> 22/02/1999

O District 10, Ho Chi Minh City.

(a) darleigh.com | LinkedIn

O MBTI: INFJ

Brief introduce

I genuinely want to use technology in my life to increase efficiency and provide long-term benefit for society. I believe that I have the qualities necessary to succeed. These qualities are demonstrated by my academic and extracurricular experiences.

Education

Bachelors, Ton Duc Thang University.

(2017-Expect 2023)

Software Engineering, GPA 7.2/10.

Class director: Good Rating.

Spiritual unity among 87 classmates to

grow together in knowledge and

common activities.

+46 Certifications

IIBA Business Analyst Foundations Communicate

Google Project Management

Google UX Designer

Google Analytics

Google IT Python

IIG TOEIC R&L 530

Google Digital Marketing 9LX 7AB 5MF

Presentation

Critical Thinking

Problem Analysis

Decision-making

Negotiation

Agile Foundations

Experience

BlockchainWork (10/2022-11/2022)

Digital Solution R&D • Webframe • Agile

In charge of current web3 product research and development, which includes:

- Analyze superiors' requirements and provide solutions to challenges.
- Create function for website to manage stakeholder and enhance user experience UIX.
- Describe the system's SRS document.

Luong Thanh Phat Company (05/2022 - 08/2022)

Techinical Collaborator • Django • Waterfall

Web applications provide digital transformation and processization of contract administration, enhanced tram information, and car rental partners using software.

HongHanh Wedding Services (05/2022 - Present)

Technical Co-Founder • Product Designer • Sales • Leadership • Waterfall

Applying digital transformation involves the use of cloud technologies in task management and work assignment to other jobs. Furthermore, self-employment allows me to better grasp the duties and processes involved in optimizing the efficiency of overtime labor.

Jobnet Vietnam (10/2020-02/2021)

UIX Designer Intern · Visual Designer · Webapp

In this employment, I was taught in fundamental programming abilities and website expertise, storing data about websites such as LandingPage, eCommerce.